roofontop.com 2013-10-25

# Privacy Policy | Legal | roofontop.com

## Privacy Policy

**Roofontop.com** is committed to maintain and protect your privacy and maintain high standards of secured transactions. This policy aims to explain you what information we require, how it is disseminated and how it is protected.

**Roofontop.com** is operated by ROT Internet Ventures Pvt. Ltd. The term, "we", "us", "our website" is referred to as roofontop.com

## Information required by roofontop.com

To use and access certain sections of our website (roofontop.com), that are restricted to only registered users, you need to create an account on roofontop.com. To create an account on roofontop.com, you will need to enter your email address and mobile number. You have to agree to the Terms & Conditions before registering an account on roofontop.com.0

## Personal Information

  * When you are registering on roofontop.com, you will need to enter you email id, mobile number and a password, which is used to protect your account from any unauthorized access. We use industry standard measures to ensure your password and personal information is protected in our database.
  * Roofontop.com may ask you for some personal information to provide you with efficient services. For these purposes, we will require you to verify this information from time to time. By using this site, you agree to provide accurate information and will cooperate with the roofontop.com personnel to ensure accuracy. 
  * Any registered user on roofontop.com, can create a profile with your personal information, photos and other content. These details can be viewed by everyone who is using and accessing the website. Roofontop.com is not liable for any misuse or misrepresentation of your profile picture or personal details. 
  * When sending messages through the roofontop.com website, we will collect and maintain information associated with each message such as, email id, phone number and the content.
  * When sending and receiving SMS to and from roofontop.com, we will collect and maintain information associated with each message such as your mobile number, the content, date and time and the wireless carrier associated with the mobile number , for logging purposes.
  * We are very serious about the privacy of our users. 

## Sharing Information

  * Roofontop.com may share your Information with carefully screened third-party service providers for the sole purpose of providing you with the services and information you have requested. Examples of such third-party service providers are credit card authorization companies. 
  * Roofontop.com may share your information with carefully screened third-party service providers for marketing purposes. Roofontop.com may send you information on new products, apps, new products, newsletters and promotions. 

## General Provisions

By agreeing to post a property listing or requirement at roofontop.com or by using any of the services of roofontop.com, or by responding to roofontop.com or by advertising on roofontop.com, the user hereby agrees and allows roofontop.com, its partners and other users of the site to contact them from time to time to keep you informed about events, tenants, potential buyers, properties that you might be interested in, real estate agents etc. 

## Laws and Regulations

Roofontop.com may be required by law to disclose your personal information to authorized law enforcement agencies. This might happen when you bring legal action against anyone who has committed any legal offence as per stated laws and regulations. 

If you have any concerns or questions regarding the security & privacy policies on roofontop.com, please contact us on [support@roofontop.com](mailto:support@roofontop.com).
